http://www.flyfishingcanada.net/privacy_policy

Contact Us
Last Update: February 21, 2007Fly Fishing Canada respects the privacy of individuals and organizations that we deal with. This notice describes our privacy policy.1. Acceptance of TermsBy using Fly Fishing Canada's website, you consent to the collection and use by Fly Fishing Canada of Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. 2. Collection of InformationTwo types of information may be collected on the Fly Fishing Canada website: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. "Personal Information" is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, e-mail address and credit card information. At the time of collection we will set out clearly the information that we are collecting and the purposes for which we will use it. It is always your choice whether or not to provide Personal Information. If you choose not to provide requested Personal Information, you will not be able to use certain features of the website and you will not be able to engage in transactions through the website. The following is a list of the means by which Fly Fishing Canada may collect Personal Information on this website:Communications from you; Registration and contact forms; Purchases; and Surveys. "Non-Personal Information" is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address), the domain used to access the Fly Fishing Canada website, and the type and version of browser or operating system being used. Aggregate information, such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors, what pages users access or visit, search requests, average time spent on this website, and information volunteered by the user, such as survey information, is also considered Non-Personal Information. Business contact information such as the name, title, business address or telephone number of a business or professional person or an employee of an organization is not considered Personal Information. Non-Personal Information is collected or derived by us in the course of operating this website. For example, our web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information which is provided through your browser or stored on a Cookie when you choose to visit the Fly Fishing Canada website. A "Cookie" is a small text file that our web server places on a user's computer hard drive to be a unique identifier. Fly Fishing Canada may use Cookies to track usage patterns and deliver customized content to users. Our Cookies do not collect personally-identifiable information. 3. Use of InformationFly Fishing Canada collects information only for the following purposes: To effect registrations for, and conduct, fly fishing and conservation related events, including without limitation, our national fly fishing championships and conservation symposia and fly fishing clinics To conduct market and membership analysis; To conduct website analysis; To effect member communications; To process transactions and payments; and To meet legal and regulatory requirements. For example, users who provide information may receive, from time to time, email announcements (e.g., regarding new inventory or special offers) and/or newsletters. You have the option to not receive these types of communications. Furthermore, the information will also be used to create customer profiles based on browsing or purchasing history. Please note that we will not supplement information collected on our website with data from other sources. In addition, we will not share data with any third parties without a user's express consent. We may offer links to other websites. For example, you may be directed to a third party credit card processing website to properly process your online order. The privacy policies of such third parties are not under our control and may differ from ours. If you have any doubts about the privacy of the information you are providing on another website, we recommend that you contact that website directly for more information and review its privacy policy. 4. Security of InformationFly Fishing Canada protects user information with the following security measures: secure servers; firewalls; username/password authentication; and other technology and procedures used to protect consumer privacy. We have reasonable security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and interception by third parties of the information under our control. However, complete confidentiality and security is not yet possible over the Internet. We assume no liability for any damages you may suffer as a result of interception, alteration or misuse of information (including your Personal Information) transmitted over the Internet. It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. 5. Disclosure of InformationFly Fishing Canada will not transfer Personal Information to third parties, except for our business partners who have agreed to comply with legally required privacy standards, and who will use the information only for the purposes disclosed at the time of collection or for a use consistent with that purpose. From time to time we may employ third parties to help us improve our website. These third parties may have limited access to databases of website user information or registered member information solely for the purpose of helping us to improve the website and they will not be able to use the information about our users for any other purpose. We may disclose your Personal Information if we are required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary or appropriate to: (a) conform to or comply with any law, regulation or court order; (b) protect and defend our rights or property or that of our suppliers, whether or not required to do so by law; or (c) protect the personal safety of users of our site or the public. We also reserve the right to disclose personal information to appropriate authorities at our discretion when it appears that activities are occurring which are illegal. We may disclose Personal Information in some other limited circumstances, but we will specifically describe them to you when we collect the information, such as in the terms of use for a new service. 6. RetentionFly Fishing Canada will keep your Personal Information for as long as it remains necessary for the identified purpose or as required by law, which may extend beyond the termination of our relationship with you. If you request that your name be removed from our databases, it may not be possible to completely delete all your Personal Information due to technological and legal constraints. 7. Access and AccuracyYou have the right to access your Personal Information to verify the Personal Information that we have collected in respect of you. Upon receipt of your written request, we will provide you with a copy of your information. We will make every reasonable effort to keep your Personal Information accurate and up-to-date, and we will enable you to revise the Personal Information as appropriate. Having accurate Personal Information about you enables us to give you the best possible service. You can help by keeping us informed of any changes such as a change of address or telephone number. If you would like to access your information, or if you find any errors in our information about you, please send us an email. Fly Fishing Canada will endeavor to deal with all such requests for access and modifications in a timely manner. 8. Changes to our Privacy PolicyFly Fishing Canada reserves the right to change this privacy policy at any time and will post an appropriate notice on the Fly Fishing Canada home page. Any change to this Privacy Policy will become effective on the date the change is posted and will apply to information collected from the date of the posting of the revised Privacy Policy and to existing information held by Fly Fishing Canada. The date on which the latest update was made is indicated at the top of this document. We recommend that you print a copy of this Privacy Policy for your reference and revisit this policy from time to time to ensure you are aware of any changes. Continued use of the Fly Fishing Canada website signifies your acceptance of any changes to the policy.9. Contact UsIf you have any concerns about privacy at Fly Fishing Canada, please send us an email. If we do not resolve an issue to your satisfaction, you may file a complaint with the Privacy Commissioner of Canada by writing to:The Privacy Commissioner of Canada112 Kent Street Ottawa , ONK1A 1H3
Copyright © 2006-2016, Fly Fishing Canada, All Rights Reserved
Terms Of Use | Privacy Policy | Powered by Quicksilk
